I don't know.
Hey, Alexandra.
Yeah, I do.
Come on in.
So have a seat.
No problem.
So you're here for the private lessons, right?
Yes.
I want to learn about black history.
You want to learn about black history?
Yes.
You sure you're prepared to learn about that?
Um, I think so.
I mean it's a long, dark journey.
You sure you can handle everything that comes with that?
That's a lot of information.
Yeah, I really want to stay in the US, so I need to know about this.
I mean, black history is a long, dark journey.
Like I said, it's a lot of information.
You can handle it?
I think we should try.
Okay, well, we can start at the beginning.
Let's see if you can understand this part.
So you know where black history starts, right?
I don't know anything about it.
You don't know anything?
So you got a lot to learn.
So you got to make sure that you listen real close, okay?
Now the beginning of black history, it starts with slavery.
You know about slavery?
Um, yes.
I don't think you know about slavery.
I heard about it.
Yeah, you've heard about it, but you ever been chained up?
Never.
You never felt the weight of a chain around your neck?
Well, you're here today to learn.
So you're going to feel like, you're going to feel the weight of the ancestors today,
okay?
Come here.
This is going to be a very hands-on lesson.
Because when you a slave, you got to listen.
You hear me?
Yes, professor.
So you got to do anything I say.
You hear me?
Anything, yes.
You're going to listen, right?
And you can't do nothing about it.
When you a slave, you can't do nothing about it.
Get on your knees.
Let's see if you can pass this class.
Because in order to stay here, you got to learn about everything.
Move your fucking hand, bitch.
See?
You already fucking up.
When you a slave, you got to listen.
You hear me, bitch?
Open your fucking mouth.
Oh shit.
You're going to learn today.
You hear me, bitch?
You don't know nothing about slaves.
You from Europe.
I'm going to teach you today.
Open wider.
Pretty slick.
So what happened when you a fucking slave, bitch?
You do what the fuck I say.
You having fun?
You ain't supposed to be having fun as a slave, bitch.
Open your fucking mouth.
Oh shit.
Yes.
That's how you learn.
Hands on.
Yes, you're a pin, bitch.
Don't move that chain.
Leave that chain right there.
You a slave, bitch.
Tell me you a slave to black dick and bitch.
I'm a slave to black dick.
Open your fucking mouth.
Get back to learning.
I'm going to violate you.
Oh yeah, you going to learn about that, too.
Open your fucking mouth, bitch.
This ain't the only lesson.
Can't even fit my whole dick in there.
Can you, bitch?
Oh yeah.
Put my dick back in your mouth.
Fucking slut.
This is the beginning.
This is just the beginning of the lesson.
This private lesson is going to last all night, okay?
It's heavy?
You feel that weight?
Don't move, bitch.
Weight European muff.
This is the weight European muff.
You sold my ancestors, bitch.
Now you got to learn about this.
You got to learn what you did.
You got to learn what you did, bitch.
I feel good as hell, bitch.
Get up there.
Yes.
Face that way.
Right there.
Got a little up somewhere.
You got a fucking muff.
Fucking girl.
Yes.
Let's learn.
This is just the beginning, bitch.
This is just the beginning.
Pretty little white bitch.
Make sure you see that black dick in there.
Oh shit.
I'm a teacher professor.
Say that again, bitch.
Teach you what?
What you here to learn?
Teach me how to take black dick.
This is the first step.
Open your fucking muff.
Yeah.
Yeah, we got to fill every hole in this.
This is the first step.
You got to know.
You got to know you're going to take every fucking inch of this black dick and every fucking hole you got, bitch.
I'm going to get you.
Give me some white pussy.
You want to give me some white pussy?
That's the right answer.
You got to do what a nigga say.
Now you got to do what a nigga say.
Yes, professor.
Good white bitches, y'all.
Listen to niggas.
That's what y'all supposed to do.
I'm going to make you get this.
Oh shit.
I need that white pussy.
I need that pure white pussy.
Yes.
This how you came to the private lesson?
That's how you came to the private lesson?
Yes, sir.
You ready to learn?
Yes.
Yes, look how she walked in.
This is how this white bitch walked in.
I'm going straight in your ass, bitch.
Oh shit.
Yo, this tight.
Oh shit, you can't give a nigga this.
You can't.
Oh my God.
Professor.
That shit stuck.
Guess how.
I'm going to stretch this hole out.
This tight as fuck.
Don't move, bitch.
I'm going straight in your ass.
No, it's going.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Straight in your ass, bitch.
That's the first lesson.
Oh shit.
You better not run either, bitch.
I'll catch you.
You a slave.
You ain't going nowhere, bitch.
Yes.
Oh fuck.
Oh, that's tight.
You're a white pussy.
It's your ass.
It's tight as fuck.
Where that black dick at?
Oh my ass, professor.
You told me that.
I have to do everything you say.
Everything a nigga say.
Why do we get?
Everything.
Oh fuck.
Oh.
Why you got to listen?
Huh?
You don't know, do you?
Uh-uh.
You a slave, bitch.
That's why you got to listen.
I'm a slave.
You a fucking slave.
Say you a slave.
I'm a slave.
Yes.
I don't know anything about black.
Owned by niggas.
You owned by niggas.
You see that European white bitch?
Take your ass to Africa.
Take your ass to Africa, bitch.
Yes.
You got to learn about all black history.
You got to start in Africa.
So the niggas take you.
Like that.
Professor.
It's pure white pussy.
White pussy.
Oh fuck.
I said you got to put this to ass.
I forgot it's to ass.
I'm going to straighten this bitch ass.
That's how I get that shit to be the tiniest fuck.
I need that shit.
Shit.
Fuckin' like you.
I told you it's a long lesson, right?
Yes.
Didn't I tell you?
You ready to learn?
Mm-hmm.
Ready to learn?
You know where it's going?
Tell me where it's going.
Ass.
Ready your white asshole.
Ready your ass.
Shit.
It closed up on you.
They don't clean it up anymore.
Yeah.
What the fuck?
It's too big.
Yo, no.
It's going to fit.
I just came out this shit.
And that shit closed up now.
Give me that shit.
Yeah.
You trying to cheat me.
I just came out that shit.
I'm gonna give you some more ass, bitch.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
That shit closed.
What the fuck?
That shit's tighter, bitch.
Why that shit's tighter, bitch?
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna violate you.
It's so big.
Ooh.
This the lesson you came for?
Yes, please.
Yes, professor.
You ready to learn?
Professor, I'm ready to learn.
Make sure you're ready to learn.
Yeah.
I'll go slow.
Damn this.
Oh, fuck.
Professor.
Where my black dick at?
It's too big.
My ass.
They're too big, bitch.
You don't take that.
Slavery is too big, bitch.
Slavery is too big.
They can't say this.
Yeah.
You gonna take this.
You gotta learn.
You gotta learn, white bitch.
Yes.
See, there you go.
There you go.
Yeah.
Don't you try to fight back, bitch.
Don't you try to, yeah, there you go.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Please, I'm gonna see my pussy.
You want your pussy?
You need to have a nigger baby.
Can't have a nigger baby if I'm nutting your asshole.
You can't have a nigger baby if I'm nutting your asshole.
That ass tight as fuck, though.
I can go back.
I ain't gonna ask you a slave.
I ain't gonna ask you for shit, bitch.
You know what you want.
What the fuck?
Let me get some more ass real quick.
If you can give me one of this, buddy.
Yes.
Tell me you own my black dick.
I own my black dick.
Yeah.
Only for niggas.
I own my own ass.
Yeah.
Because you a slave, bitch.
Oh, my God.
Slave to niggas.
Good ass.
Let me get some pussy.
I got some pussy.
That's why I was afraid to listen.
That's the long story.
Oh.
You can feel that shit different.
You can feel that European pussy different.
This don't feel like no American bitch.
This is that European pussy.
This is that pure shit.
You can feel that different.
Oh.
No nigga's supposed to be in here.
Thanks.
Hey, no nigga's supposed to be in here.
Yeah.
Pure white pussy.
Oh.
This is a little bit scary.
It's just gonna be a little bit scary bitch.
Let's just do it.
Oh.
Shit.
You.
Pussy, good as hell.
Here's a bitch pussy, good as hell.
This pussy's just moving.
Ah.
This is funny.
Oh.
Ah.
This is funny.
Oh.
Oh
You don't know what I'm gonna do to you tonight, bitch
I'm trying to learn about black history. It's a lot to learn bitch. That's years years bitch
It's for the ancestors for the ancestors bitch
Where you going bitch move your fucking hand
Oh
The years you for life bitch you a slave for life
Niggas only niggas only me and my niggas don't do whatever the fuck we want to you
Bitch I want some more ass
Oh
Yo
Dicks than this first bitch
Oh
We're not like the capital is work
And this white bitch ass
European white bitch asshole
This shit will need to be stretched out
You'll be at home in your cabin just chilling sore from all this work you doing today bitch
Slaves work so it's gotta do piece with slaves gotta do you get one day off is your ass good? That's it
Oh
Try to break your chains bitch way going nowhere way going nowhere bitch. I'm still fuck your asshole
Yes
Yes, yes
Rebecca us
This is your job.
This is your job, I appreciate it.
You're a pain, I love it.
I love it.
Niggas ain't supposed to be there.
There's no niggas in Europe.
Oh, bud.
Oh.
It's okay.
Let me get in there real quick.
Let me get in there.
I'm in my own now.
Yes.
I'm on my niggas.
Oh my God.
My daddy's true dad.
My dad.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
This is something I like to call my sister, Printer.
Printer, yes.
Yes.
You'll be a good slut.
Yes, Professor Richard.
I'm gonna be a good slut for you.
Yeah.
You're a slut.
I'm gonna use all my muscles today.
Yes.
Yeah.
My balls are much bigger.
You nasty bitch.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, no.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
You know where it's going, right?
I'm gonna ask Professor.
Ah.
Oh, fuck.
No.
Oh, shit.
That's what you're supposed to be.
That's what white bitches do now.
That's the new slavery.
Get it.
It's like pure European one.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Yes.
Ah.
I gotta feel the back of your shit.
I gotta feel it.
I gotta get off.
I gotta get to know my property.
Ah.
Yes.
You take one second, zero, this leg's gonna go
right back in your asshole, bitch.
Oh, my God.
Right back in your asshole, bitch.
Get this shit.
I'm so, I'm so.
I'm so.
Ah.
Oh, my God.
You might take a few nuts, bitch.
You might have to take a few nuts.
Where that black nigga at?
I'm gonna ask Professor.
Ah.
White bitch.
I'm gonna ask him.
You nasty white bitch.
Yeah.
It's the lesson.
It's the lesson when you come around niggas.
It's what you gotta learn.
I'm gonna ask Professor.
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
Yeah.
I know it's a lot, but you gonna take it.
Yes, Professor.
You gonna take it.
I'm gonna take it.
You gonna do a good slip?
Yes, Professor.
Yeah.
I'm gonna take it.
Ah.
You.
Mm-hmm.
Ah.
No.
You're gonna fuck me all night.
You can't prepare it, though.
He's Professor.
She can't with that butt plug in her head.
Yes.
That's a good student.
That's a bitch you wanna learn.
I'm gonna be a good student.
You already started off on the right foot, bitch.
It's Professor.
Ah.
This ass is so good.
Ha ha ha.
Professor.
No, you were.
Ha ha ha.
Ah.
Yes.
Ha ha ha.
No nigga like me.
Ain't no one that these niggas like me.
Yes.
You're property.
You gotta do what I say.
Yes, Professor.
Ah.
Yes.
Cry all you want to, I'ma still fuck your asshole, bitch.
I'ma still fuck your asshole, bitch.
Yes, Professor.
All of you on my body.
That's my body, you my property.
Yes.
That's your body, it's your body.
Ha ha ha ha.
Yes.
This right here, what niggas need.
White bitches who listen.
Yes.
Pure European white bitches who listen.
That's the American dream.
Ha.
Throw that ass, bitch.
Yes.
Ah.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
You need to go stay in your shell.
Okay.
Ah.
You put your milk in my ass.
You're such a fucking asshole.
You're such a fucking bitch.
You're such a bitch.
Ah.
Oh my God.
That's why you came over here.
Yes.
Yes, Professor.
You're such a bitch.
I'ma shit you.
Say it.
Say it again, bitch.
You're such a bitch.
Me?
Yeah.
You're such a bitch.
I'ma shit you.
White bitch can't even learn.
Pure white bitch can't even learn.
Yeah.
Ah.
Fuck.
Here.
My nigga's got bigger dicks.
Yes.
Niggas next got bigger dicks, bitch.
Oh my God.
Yeah, bitch.
You're such a bitch.
Oh my God.
This is just the first lesson.
Yeah.
Ah.
Ah, shit.
Ah, fuck.
Yeah.
Ah.
You're gonna take them every day.
Yup.
You're gonna take a different nigga every day.
Monday through Saturday.
Sunday you get off.
That's for real.
That's for real, bitch.
Ah.
White bitch can't even see the bruises.
Fuck.
Ah.
Oh, fuck.
Yo.
Ah, shit.
Ah.
Yo.
You a truth, bitch.
Taking all this dick.
Oh, fuck that.
Oh, no.
You keep crying.
You're hurting me.
Ah.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, man.
Get on your fucking knees, bitch.
It's your fucking asshole white bitch.
Oh, shit.
Your chain's off enough.
Yeah.
Ah.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
My ass tastes so good.
Sweet fucking asshole.
Sweet tight asshole.
Yes.
Ah, shit.
Good throat, too.
White bitch got good throat, too.
Oh, fuck.
Right now I wanna see my ass.
See?
See what you did?
See how?
What?
You got a nigga wanna stay in your asshole.
Ah.
You're not telling me.
That's how I was born.
Yeah.
Ah.
Pretty slut.
Pretty slut, yeah.
Oh, shit.
There you go, you pretty bitch.
You pretty white bitch.
You see that pretty face?
Open your fucking mouth, bitch.
Right there.
Yeah.
Ah.
There you go.
Little ass mouth.
That little ass mouth.
You here to learn?
Mm-hmm.
You gonna be a good student?
Yeah, shit.
This is the oral presentation.
It's your oral presentation, bitch.
You nasty white bitch.
Ah.
Thank you, professor.
I want some more ass.
Ah, shit, so good.
Yo.
Ah.
Swear you're a European bitch is different.
You European bitch is different.
You gotta get you a European bitch.
Yeah.
Ah, shit.
Yo.
Oh.
Shit.
Ah.
Oh.
Got a nigga dick hard as hell.
And you ain't even supposed to be in here.
You supposed to go your whole life without seeing a nigga.
Now I'm in your mouth, bitch.
Now you got a nigga in your mouth, bitch.
Yeah.
That's what happened in America.
It's different over here, bitch.
You like America?
Say you love America, bitch.
We got the real niggas over here.
We got the real niggas in America.
You ain't got this shit in Europe.
Oh.
Shut the fuck up.
You gotta learn that too.
You gotta learn that too, bitch.
That's a real important lesson.
That's my favorite lesson.
Oh.
That's my favorite.
Bitch.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
That was a whole lesson for your real hands, bitch.
You just want that pretty face in there.
That pretty face in there.
That's it.
Like an asshole.
Yes.
Yeah.
Good slug.
Keep doing that.
Just like that, bitch.
Oh, shit.
So slazy.
That's that soul food.
Put your whole head.
Oh, fuck.
Just like that.
That's a good slug, yo.
Oh, fuck.
Just like that, bitch.
Oh, shit.
This slag's getting set free.
This is what this bitch did.
Damn.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Dirty asshole.
That's all.
Yo.
Yeah.
You need your food.
You gotta.
Oh.
Eat something.
Eat some more.
Yo.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, damn.
Damn, bitch.
Oh, fuck.
That felt good, I say.
Yo.
Oh, shit.
Yes.
Oh.
You're gonna be choked.
Yeah.
It's a good slug, yeah.
Oh, bitch.
Yes.
Oh.
Oh, bitch.
Yo.
This is what a nigga be.
Nah.
What if I just wanna do that every day with everybody?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, you gotta do this with all the bitches.
You gotta do this with all the bitches.
Mm-hmm.
Make sure they know that shit.
Make sure they know that shit, buddy.
Just do it.
Say it.
oon't bread well.
We need to edit.
OK.
I made a little forest down this road,
AC mister.
No, it's not really not it's not what it is,
it's not really not cool at all with just this shit.
Uh.
In the cooler.
Yeah.
Yes.
You need a fucking mouth.
You need a fucking mouth, bitch.
It's a long lesson.
It's a long lesson on black history, bitch.
You gotta learn.
You gotta learn this whole thing.
Pretty bitch.
Yeah.
It's okay.
Oh.
Yeah.
I'm gonna be some asshole in a second, bitch.
Oh, please.
I wanna feel in my ass again.
Please.
Look at me, bitch.
Oh.
Keep that shit in there, bitch.
I know that black dick not supposed to be in there.
He's supposed to be black in the European.
It's not as hard to fit in the European,
my friend May fit his little dick.
He's supposed to fit big black dicks in there.
Shut the fuck up.
Yo.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, Professor.
You enjoying your private lesson?
Very.
So what bitches need to learn about?
Black dick.
Yeah, that's what you need to learn about
when you come to America, bitch.
Mm-hmm.
With that black dick in your mouth.
Yes, Professor.
What?
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh.
Black dick.
You.
Oh.
Mm.
Yeah, I need some rest.
I need some rest.
Mm.
Oh.
Yes.
Mm.
You're like an animal.
Yes.
Oh my God.
You're like an asshole.
Mm.
Oh.
Mm, shit, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh, professor.
Mm-mm.
Mm.
Bloody asshole, bitch.
Oh.
Oh my God.
That shit gripping like it's supposed to.
Yeah.
It's a little white ass gripping like it's supposed to,
like a nigga ain't ever been in there.
Like niggas ain't never been in there before.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Oh my God.
Oh, shit.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Mm.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
That's part of the lesson.
Oh.
That's part of the lesson, bitch.
Yes, professor.
Mm.
You want to be a good student?
Yes, professor.
Mm.
Shit.
That's what good students do.
Mm.
Hands on lessons.
Hands on private lessons.
Yes, you want to make sure.
It's why bitch want to make sure.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Ew.
This asshole.
Yeah.
This is what I'm talking about.
Make sure you're ready to learn.
Make sure you're ready to learn, bitch.
Mm.
Ew.
Oh, shit.
Mm.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Yeah.
Mm.
You want to eat your pussy?
Oh.
Keep it in your ass.
Please.
You got a choice now.
See, it's segregation.
Please.
You out of slavery.
It's just segregated.
You got a choice, bitch.
Oh.
You want it in your pussy or your ass, bitch?
Open my ass, please.
Yeah, I'm gonna keep it in there.
Oh, shit.
Good white bitch.
Yeah.
Yep.
Oh.
Good slut.
That's what good white bitches do.
Good white bitch.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
All right.
I'm gonna keep, I'm gonna open you up more, bitch.
Then you gonna open this white ass up more, bitch.
Yeah.
Yo.
Yes.
Oh.
Say it again, bitch.
Thank you, professor.
Yes.
Oh.
There you go.
That's a good slut, see.
You like to learn.
This white bitch like to learn.
She wanna stay in America.
You wanna stay in America?
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
You my mother.
That's what niggas need.
That's what you need to do to stay in America, bitch.
Fuck.
You're not gonna own my mama.
Yeah.
You my slave still, bitch.
You're not gonna own my slave.
Yeah.
Oh.
Fuck.
Yes.
Yes, that open asshole.
Yeah.
It's a little more.
Fuck.
Yes, that's a good slut.
That's a good slut.
Fuck.
Oh.
Yeah.
One more.
Fuck him off.
Fuck him off right there.
You gotta take this elective.
Gotta take this elective on.
I don't like music.
Let me hear you, bitch.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Pretty white bitch.
Get your fucking mouth.
You here to learn?
Pretty white bitch here to learn?
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, fuck.
That sweet slut right there.
Nigga can't stay out your asshole too long.
Nigga can't stay out your asshole too long, bitch.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit, damn.
Oh, my God.
Damn.
Oh, no.
Ew.
You gonna get fucked all night.
All night, bitch.
So you gonna take night classes?
Yeah.
Yeah, you gotta graduate, bitch.
Make that easier.
Yeah.
Right in this bitch's asshole.
Yes.
Don't move, bitch.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Let me teach you.
Yeah.
Say please, professor.
Yes, professor.
Oh, shit.
You're gonna want me.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
You gonna be my favorite student.
Yeah, you be my, that's even better.
That's even better, bitch.
You a slave.
Fuck the 14th Amendment, bitch.
You a white slave.
Yep, my white slave.
It's your only job.
Take niggas' dicks in your ass, bitch.
Look at that shit.
Look at this shit.
Good white bitch.
Good white bitch, you know what I mean?
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Teach her the year.
Show me you appreciate me.
Show me you appreciate black dick.
Straight up your asshole, bitch.
That sweet asshole.
Yo.
You know how to suck black dick.
You move through this lesson quick, bitch.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yo.
Oh, boy, what is you care, bitch?
That's it.
That's it, bitch.
All this time.
That's a big black dick, ain't it?
Open your fucking mouth, bitch.
This is how we treat white bitches in America.
We ain't used to that in Europe.
We ain't years without seeing niggas in Europe.
We see you now, bitch.
Me and all my niggas.
Yes, professor.
Suck my fucking dick.
That's it.
Oh, no.
Don't you go in your asshole again.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Motherfucking bitch, though.
Yo.
Hey.
Best type of white bitch.
Bitch.
You're sitting in a little mug.
I forgot about that.
That little asshole, I know it closed up.
You open it right back.
You open it right back,
but you gotta suck dick right quick.
Yeah.
Pretty bitch.
Pretty white bitch, suck my dick.
Put on that too.
Yeah, look at me.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yo.
You already learned it?
Mm-hmm.
You already learned it, shit.
Professor, can I see your dick?
Yes.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Oh.
Don't move that.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Slow.
You're slow.
Get that in there.
Let me get that in there.
Let me.
There we go.
Good girl.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
It's not good, no?
No, it's just if you make it harder.
No, suck my dick.
Oh, fucking dick.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck.
Pretty bitch.
Pretty bitch, damn.
Yes.
I'm gonna violate you, you sexy ass.
Open.
Open that shit.
I'm gonna go asshole in one second.
Let me get that.
Let me get this right quick.
Yeah.
Let me get this right here.
Give me some ass.
There you go.
Fuck.
Oh.
Just like that, bitch.
You got a lot to learn.
You got a lot to learn, white bitch.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Ah.
Good girl.
Oh my God.
There you go.
Just like that, bitch.
Just like that, white bitch.
You gonna listen?
That's what good white bitches do.
Suck a nigga dick then take that shit in the ass.
Your tight little white asshole.
Good soft European asshole.
It's that quality.
Tell me you don't have black dick in Europe.
I don't have black dick in Europe.
Not that American dick.
It's different.
Yeah.
That's why I'm in the US.
That's why you came to America?
Yeah, that's why I'm in the US.
Yes, that's why I came to America.
Keep going, bitch.
Nigga might nut in your ass, bitch.
Tight asshole.
Sweet fucking white asshole.
That's what good white bitches do.
That's what good white bitches learn about.
Shut the fuck up, bitch.
Yeah.
That's part of the lesson too.
You have to stay in the asshole.
Stay in the asshole.
Yes.
Niggas need this shit.
That's what you need to do to pass.
You gotta take this black dick.
You gotta.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
No.
Oh.
Oh shit.
No.
Pretty white bitch.
Thank you, professor.
That's what good students do.
Thank you.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
It's the dingo.
Ah shit.
Marco...
Marcoiche...
Marcoiche.
Marco.
No!
You fuck!
ex
list
live
ike
it
ok
mm-hmm
yeah
no
I'm
Done.
Ooooh
Alright..
Str my bozo
I saled it on there
Filborne.
...
Still come off fucking
Oh
You can take ten hours of black dick in there
I
As all lessons
Swear to nigga me keep doing this
In America you please niggas, it's the other way around over here you gotta learn about niggas
Bitches
I'm a little extra low your efficiency
and make y'all different over there.
Feel the European white bitch.
That's why that shit's so soft.
That's that quality.
That European shit.
Just like that bitch.
Yeah.
Taking you to Africa, the last stop.
That's the last stop, bitch.
You want American niggas back.
Tell me you want to go to Africa.
I want to go to Africa.
Say it again, bitch.
Professor.
We're going to do study abroad in Africa.
Yes.
You ready to do study abroad in Africa?
Mm-hmm.
Take international niggas.
Listen.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, shit.
This is how you control niggas.
Yeah.
You don't want here to learn, no.
You're supposed to learn about black dick.
That's how you do it.
That's how you control niggas.
Sucking niggas dick.
Get his foot.
My foot is going to be only black milk every day.
Yep.
When I ask.
Soul food is all you get.
Peace and black milk.
That's it.
Mm-hmm.
Just like that bitch.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, shit.
Pretty little white bitch.
That's what you're supposed to be.
You're supposed to be on your knees sucking black dick.
Mm-hmm.
It's my place.
Ah.
Oh, shit.
Tell me your purpose is to suck black dick.
Oh.
My purpose is to suck black dick.
Yes.
The European bitch.
Mm-hmm.
So having the big European bitches, they come to America, they start sucking black dick.
Ah, shit.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Is that it?
You don't let a nigga put it in your asshole?
Mm-hmm.
You don't let a nigga put it in your asshole, bitch?
Yeah.
Give me some ass.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, my God.
I know that she closed the door.
Ah.
Mm-hmm.
Fuck.
Ah.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Professors, please, please.
Ain't too big, bitch.
Shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up, bitch.
Oh, my God.
It's all good.
I'm sorry.
Ah.
It's, uh, shit.
Yo, I said gripping her.
I said gripping her, bitch.
You say it's too big.
You can take that.
You can take bigger, bitch.
You know what, I'm going to get you in this fucking mess.
Don't you forget, bitch.
Ugh.
I'm sorry.
Good, tight, white asshole.
Nigga can't stay out of this shit.
You know what used to happen to niggas who would do this shit, bitch?
The fuck?
Take all that, and that.
Nigga can't take all that, and that.
What you all going to do?
What the niggas going to do?
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Get off me.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Stay in your shell.
Where's the, where's my black dick at?
In my ass, professor.
This is my ass.
This.
This ass is so deep.
Where'd it go?
There it is.
That's the music.
Oh, my God.
Please.
Yes.
Say that again.
Please, professor.
I'm going to break your asshole tonight, bitch.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Bitch.
Let me slide out there for a second and close up.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
That was good.
Oh, shit.
Yo.
Please, give me a break, please.
Oh, shit.
Fuck you, I'm going to break your ass.
You got to learn the whole thing.
Oh, yes.
They don't teach you this in school.
You got to learn this whole shit before you come to America, bitch.
Yes, professor.
We got niggas over here.
There's niggas over here.
I'm going to learn every day.
Yep, every day.
You got to learn every day.
Make sure you assimilate into America, bitch.
Every day.
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Pure white European.
That's what the Dutch would make.
It's pure white European asshole.
Yes.
Oh, please.
Please, professor.
Please.
Good blending, my girl.
It's softer European.
Niggas will get this every day.
Niggas will get you, bitch.
It's like you have to go.
Oh, yes.
No.
Why does he get...
Are you kidding me?
You have to sleep.
I'm wet.
Oh.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah.
Give me, give me, bitch.
You should wake.
You should put my feet like that.
You should do like this.
Oh.
Fuck.
It's so big.
No.
Fuck.
Oh.
Hey.
Pretty white bitch.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
Oh.
Give me a bit.
Give me a shit bit.
Yeah.
Fuck.
That right there.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Tell me you like learning about life dick.
Say it right now.
Say it.
Say it right now bitch.
Fuck.
That's the language you need to be speaking.
I understand that.
Niggas understand that shit.
Shit.
Garlic getting right on board See this lousy muscle
Partiture.
You gotta learn about everything, bitch.
You gotta learn about everything, white bitch.
It's what the ancestors wanted you to do.
It's what the ancestors.
Put your shit back!
Put that shit back!
It's what the ancestors, bitch.
You gotta learn now.
Yeah.
You smell this bitch.
You know what I was right there, huh?
You're gonna get it.
Oh, fuck.
We're not black dickheads.
My ass.
It's what white bitches need to learn, huh?
I want to see my ass, professor.
Oh my god.
I want to see my ass.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
This one's black dick.
Oh, fuck.
This one's what white bitches gotta do.
Oh, shit.
You wake up, you gotta suck black dick.
Get home, you gotta suck black dick.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
Oh.
Yo.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Tell me you want that black dick in your ass.
Black dick in my ass.
Black dick in my ass, professor.
Yes, every time.
Every time you come to America, what happens?
Every time when I come to America, my ass is gonna work.
By what? Big black what?
Big black dick in my ass.
This one.
Every day.
Every day in the weeks.
Ten hours a day.
Yes, look at that.
You gotta please niggas every day.
So white bitches like you may for.
Pure European white bitches for niggas.
It's the prize for niggas.
This is what niggas mean.
Pure European white bitches like you.
You suckin' black dick.
Oh, shit.
I'm gonna get killed for this shit.
Niggas killed for this shit.
Yeah.
Just like that white bitch.
That's exactly what you're supposed to do.
Good white bitch.
See, you learnin'.
You're about to pass, bitch.
You're about to pass.
You're gonna stay in America.
Stay in America and suck some more black dick.
That's what you wanna do.
Tell me you wanna stay in America.
This is what I wanna do.
I wanna take big black dick every day.
Big black American dick.
Big black American dick every day.
Take black dick.
Niggas need you for.
You suckin' my dick, bitch.
Just like that.
Yo.
I'm gonna get killed for this shit.
Just like that bitch.
Good white bitch.
Oh shit.
This is what you need to go to school for.
Suckin' black dick.
This is your lesson, bitch.
You don't need no math.
Learn English and suck black dick.
You learn English so you know what the fuck I'm saying.
And you suck black dick.
That's what you learn in school in America.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no.
I need some ass, bitch.
No, no, no.
Please take my ass.
Please take my ass, professor.
Please.
Deep in the heart.
Say please, professor.
Please, professor.
Say it again, bitch.
Please, professor. Take my asshole.
Please, professor.
Please.
Oh, my god.
Yes, professor.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, my god.
I love you. You're black.
I love you.
You're black, milk.
Oh, my god.
I can't taste it.
Just give it to me.
I'm gonna try to get you to come up.
That's your first lesson.
I'm taking me.
That's your first lesson, bitch.
Oh.
Niggas in your ass.
It's not the only lesson, bitch.
You gotta take more niggas in your ass.
Oh my God.
Put your head down.
It's so big.
What's in your asshole?
What dick?
That European asshole.
Ain't no niggas in Europe, is it?
Ain't no niggas in Europe.
I mean your asshole.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
Oh.
Fuck.
Please, I want you to come up.
I want you to black me up.
Please, professor.
Black me up in my ass.
Oh yes.
Please, professor.
I don't feel like.
Fill up your ass.
Don't fill up your asshole, bitch.
Yes.
Oh fuck.
Oh shit.
Oh.
Feel that grip, bitch.
Oh fuck.
Yo.
Fuck.
Thank you, professor.
Let me see.
Let me see your workout.
Let me see what you learned.
Oh yeah.
Oh.
It's a lot of blood milk.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
Mm.
Oh shit.
Oh.
See.
Pretty good.
Yeah.
Oh.
Are you ready for more niggas?
Yes.
Get that asshole ready for more niggas.
This is just the first lesson.
First lesson.
I need more.
Oh.
That is so good.
Let me wake you.
Oh.
This is delicious.
I want to eat it every day.
That's what you better do in America.
Mm.
That's exactly what you better do in America.
Oh.
Damn.
It's the end of the lesson.
That's what she learned.
I'm sorry.
Mm-hmm.
There's more going in there too.
Thank you for using me, Professor.
Thank you.
Lesson number one.
There's more niggas coming.